See you next time.
Catch up with Luffy.
The Straw Hats All Out Battle.
Hey, wait.
I think I know that guy with the sword.
Yeah, he's one of Straw Hat Luffy's henchmen, Pirate Hunter Zorro.
Henchman, huh?
At least he recognized me.
You're not even a henchman.
You're Pirate A.
What was that?
Maybe B.
Listen, when I get a bounty, it's going to be twice as much as yours.
Whatever, Pirate Z.
Stop changing it.
Hey, stop, you two.
I don't think they can hear you, Sniper King.
Don't worry.
It's all part of my plan.
I don't get it, but it sounds cool.
There's more of them over there.
They found us.
Some might be hiding on the train.
Blow it up.
Hey, stop.
Nami's still inside there.
Fire.
Damn it.
If they harmed a hair on her head, I swear.
Hold on a second, Pirate A.
What?
Nami isn't a background character like you.
It's going to take more than one sorry little bazooka attack to defeat her.
Listen, you henchmen, for the last time.
That hurt.
Are you okay, Sniper King?
Never better, my friend.
Wow, she's far.
What's wrong?
Save for yourself.
Hey.
Don't shoot.
I'm just an old lady.
I'm a little girl with a kitty cat.
We're too cute to dog.
The Straw Hacked Pirates threatened to do all kinds of rude and immoral stuff if I didn't operate the train for them.
Those meanies.
Who would let their hostages get drunk?
That was close.
We almost blew up that innocent old lady.
What kind of deranged monster would take a senior citizen, a little girl, and a cat as hostages?
Huh?
Is it just me or is that smoke forming a cloud?
Using cool balls and heat balls, I can turn the moisture in the air into clouds.
Oh, there you are, Nami Sweet!
I knew you'd make it out okay!
Hey, something weird's going on with that smoke cloud thing.
Look!
The cloud's growing, Granny!
Yeah!
It's starting to look dangerous if you ask me.
Come on!
Let's go!
Yeah!
He didn't name it the perfect climate hack for nothing.
These clouds are growing a lot bigger and faster than before.
The question is, how strong are the Thunderbolts?
Let's find out.
This is looking scary, guys.
It's probably better to run, right?
I hope you're ready.
Cause here comes the new Thunderbolt Tipo!
Look, look!
You can see their skeletons!
I tell ya, that girl is something else!
Hey, is this a relic gonna protect us?
Sure!
We haven't been struck by any of them lightning bolts yet, have we?
You trying to kill me or what?!
Nami, why'd you hit Sniper King?
I don't know.
I felt like it.
Don't take it out on me!
It's not my fault you don't know how to use it yet!
Besides, Usopp told me he never added a feature like that.
Either way, that thing is crazy powerful.
You beat everyone!
Damn it, Nami!
What the hell!
Watch where you aim that thing!
Apologize to him, Sniper King!
You apologize, stupid!
I haven't felt a shock like that since the first time I met you, Nami Swan!
Those pirates are out of control!
It's crazy!
I thought that girl was just a navigator, but it turns out she's just as strong as the rest of them!
Seems like the storm has passed!
That was awesome, pirate lady!
Yeah!
Hey!
Glad to see you guys made it out alive, Granny!
Ain't no coincidence I've lived as long as I have!
So anyway, what about our captain?
Any guesses on where he went?
Who knows?
The island's pretty big.
Where should we start?
Huh?
That's got to be where he's at!
Alright then.
Let's get moving.
You filthy criminals think the watchdogs will let you do as you please?
Not a chance.
A
W egy
...
sweep
with
...
Any
Now, gong gong!
He jumped onto the tree!
I'm not getting anywhere.
Don't those dumb jerks have anything better to do?
This way, quick!
They're running the other way?
Half of you, head to the main island's front gate!
Pirates forced it open and are invading the island!
Stop them at any cost!
Alright, now that everyone else is here,
I can finally stop running from these guys!
Got him!
Sorry, try again!
He's over there! Fire!
I think we should take a right.
In that case, we better turn left.
Oh, you wanna fight about it?
Guys, chill! We're just going straight!
Our idiot captain hadn't rushed ahead on his own.
We wouldn't be having this little problem right now.
Well, we're the ones following that idiot around.
So what does that make us?
Then again, thanks to Luffy,
the Marine forces are scattered all over the island!
All we have to do now is head straight for the courthouse!
Oh no! My chronic illness is back!
Then stay here and die on your own!
Acured!
That's better!
Hey! Is something wrong?
Looks like we've got guests!
We are the watchdogs, guards of the island's front gate!
You've run rampant for far too long, villains!
No criminals shall cross this line!
What's wrong? You guys can't afford horses?
Look around before you mock us, pirate scum!
Yep, I'd say they've got us surrounded all right.
Were they following us all this time?!
It's too late to run away now!
You're finished!
Yeah? We'll see.
You cocky little scoundrel!
All right men, let's...
Grab on!
There!
Thanks!
You could've let us have some fun first though!
You idiot!
Don't forget the reason you came here!
Save your energy for the real fight!
You're right!
We'd be here all day with that many guys!
Those kiddos are full of energy!
Don't die out there!
Go save your friends!
Yeah!
Everybody!
Get back!
That's a King Bolt for Water 7!
Ready the cannons!
You guys ready?
Fire!
Freaky family coming through!
Watch Dogs!
Back in formation immediately!
Roger!
You can run away if you like!
But our dogs aren't going to lose to a couple of overgrown fish!
Uh-oh!
They're gonna jump up on the boat!
What?!
Can we go any faster?!
Hey!
Cook!
Huh?
What's up?
You take the reins!
Here!
Wait!
What's going on here?
You take the reins!
Here!
Wait!
What's going on here?
Here!
When you see them!
I want you to pass on a message for me!
You're all fired!
You got it!
Alright!
Jump!
Not so fast!
Good luck, Galila!
We're leaving this one to you!
We're gonna skewer you!
I'm not get ещё!
Ah, don't!
You have to run up on the boat!
No!
It's not!
Airdrop!
EEE!
Ah!
Proud!
You have to run up.
I want you to pass on a message for me!
You're all fired!
You got it.
Alright!
Jump!
Not so fast!
Good luck, Galila!
We're leaving this one to you!
We're gonna skewer you!
I'm not...
Airdrop!
Ah!
Gah!
Whoa! He took out those watchdogs in one hit!
Fools! They just let their guard down!
No mere human can match our speed!
Give them a taste of canine power, men! Go!
They won't know what hit them!
Strike like lightning!
Not them, too!
Who are these guys?
That was so... cool!
You ready for round two?
Take this!
It seems your temperament is as volatile as ever, cruddy flam!
Even though we haven't seen each other in years, it turns out that you...
I'll see you next time.
Stop! That wasn't the agreement!
Calm now. What are you getting so worked up about?
You promised the Straw Hats would be allowed to leave Water 7 safely.
Correct. After allowing them to leave safely as promised, the Straw Hats decided to come here.
Mastered! On the next, One Piece, Robin betrayed the motive of the world government.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!